# Hjalti Unnar Agustsson

+354 847-9875 hjaltiunnar@gmail.com Reykjavik, Iceland



## Profile

I have worked with various website projects, large corporation systems and complex academic projects. I love to work with front end development and user experience overall. Always looked at myself as a leader and have great attention to detail. Great team player, humble and smart.

# Experience

#### DIRECTOR OF OPERATIONS, MAYSTAR CONSULTING; NEW YORK, USA - 2016-PRESENT

Web design consultancy. It is a start up business so I took care of many various tasks including; front end coding, design tasks, client relationship, task management, workflow, and Google Adwords.

#### PROGRAMMER, ANNATA; REYKJAVIK, ICELAND - 2015-2016

I was a back end programmer for Microsoft Dynamics AX. We were 8 team members working on updating to the new AX7. We worked with Scrum agile and I learned X++.

#### IT SUPPORT, ROBISON SCANDINAVIA; COPENHAGEN, DENMARK – 2014

I was working for a travel agency. Tasked with website projects, tour creative projects and client support. Learned more professional danish vocabulary.

#### PRODUCT OWNER, ICE-ROVERS; REYKJAVIK, ICELAND - 2013-PRESENT

My family business, we are renting out modified Land Rover Defenders. I take care of clients and the booking system. I also maintain our website.

## WEB DEVELOPER, <u>KAPTIO</u>; REYKJAVIK, ICELAND – 2012-2013

I was a website developer and I built a few Wordpress sites. Where I learned HTML, PHP and CSS. Including configuring Salesforce for customers.

### Education

VIA University College – BSC Information and communication technology engineering, Denmark 2010-2014

# Languages

ICELANDIC	ENGLISH	DANISH

Mother Language Excellent command Good command

# Hjalti Unnar Agustsson

+354 847-9875 hjaltiunnar@gmail.com Reykjavik, Iceland

## Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Chart.JS, X++, Github, Dynamics AX 7, Wordpress, PHP, Sketch, Scrum, SQL, Java, Android, Google Adwords & Analytics.

## **Hobbies**













## Portfolio

https://hjalti.design